Guide to the Rice University James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy records, 1993-2014 UA 114
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XX: James A. Baker III
  - Access Correspondence for James A. Baker III Papers, 1957-2011 at Princeton, 2 of 3, 2005-2008 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Access Correspondence for JAB III Papers, 1957-2011 at Princeton, 3 of 3, 2005-2008 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Access Correspondence for former James A. III Baker Public Service Archive, 1995-2002 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Russian-American Dialogue Project, 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - BIPP: National Geographic Maps, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Bremen University, 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - F. Djerejian Take Home Folder, 1 of 3, 2000-2012 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - F. Djerejian Take Home Folder, 2 of 3, 2000-2012 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - F. Djerejian Take Home Folder, 3 of 3, 2000-2012 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - The End Game Exhibit, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - BIPP Events and Engagements Requests for JAB, 2003-2007 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - JAB Office Suite Remodeling, 2004-2005 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Untitled Book Manuscript, 1 of 2, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Untitled Book Manuscript, 2 of 2, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Inventory of Boxes sent to Baker Institute, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - JAB Oral History Project Transcripts from George Schultz and Richard Cheney Interviews, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Work Hard, Study... and Keep Out of Politics! Uncorrected Proof, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - James Addison Baker, III, Photographer, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Tenth Anniversary of the Sadat Lecture for Peace Consent and Release Correspondence, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - The Mudd Manuscript Library Correspondence re: Margaret Tutwiler's journals, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Groundbreaking of James A. Baker Monument, 2009-2010 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, 1 of 2, 1998-2008 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, 2 of 2, 1996-1997 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Daily Schedule and Set-Up Sheets, 1996-1997 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Malcom Gillis, 1997-2001 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Subseries A: BIPP Campaign
    This subseries is restricted for the life of the creator plus 50 years.
    - Campaign Solicitations-General Prospects, 1993-1996 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Baker Institute Campaign (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Solicitations-Donor Prospects January 21, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Solicitations-Ambassadorial, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Forward Planning, 1995-1996 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Subseries B: Lectures, Speeches, and Related Events
    - Baker, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Baker, 1 of 2, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Baker, 2 of 2, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Baker, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Baker, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Baker, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Baker, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Baker, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Baker, 2000-2001 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Subseries C: The Baker Project
    - Master Transcripts 1 of 2, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Master Transcripts 2 of 2, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - B-Roll Program Notebook, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Briefing Book Information and Transcripts, 1 of 2, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Briefing Book Information and Transcripts, 2 of 2, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Subseries D: Publicity
    - Signed Photographs Photocopies, 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Personal Newsclips January-June, 1 of 3, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Personal Newsclips January-June, 2 of 3, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Personal Newsclips January-June, 3 of 3, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Personal Newsclips July-December, 1 of 3, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Personal Newsclips July-December, 2 of 3, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Personal Newsclips July-December, 3 of 3, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Personal Newsclips January-June, 1 of 2, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Personal Newsclips January-June, 2 of 2, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Personal Newsclips July-December, 1 of 2, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Personal Newsclips July-December, 2 of 2, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Photo Requests A-Z, 1 of 2, 1995-1999 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Photo Requests A-Z, 2 of 2, 1995-1999 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Book and Book Plate Signatures A-K, 1 of 3, 1995-1999 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Book and Book Plate Signatures A-K, 2 of 3, 1995-1999 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Book and Book Plate Signatures A-K, 3 of 3, 1995-1999 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Book and Book Plate Signatures L-Z, 1 of 3, 1995-2002 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Book and Book Plate Signatures L-Z, 2 of 3, 1995-2002 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Book and Book Plate Signatures L-Z, 3 of 3, 1995-2002 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Personal Newsclips January-June, 1 of 2, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Personal Newsclips January-June, 2 of 2, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Personal Newsclips July-December, 1 of 2, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Personal Newsclips July-December, 2 of 2, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Completed Interviews, 1 of 3, 1996-1997 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Completed Interviews, 2 of 3, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Completed Interviews, 3 of 3, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Personal Newsclips January-June, 1 of 2, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Personal Newsclips January-June, 2 of 2, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Personal Newsclips July-December, 1 of 2, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Personal Newsclips July-December, 2 of 2, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Press Requests, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Personal Newsclips January-December, 1 of 3, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Personal Newsclips January-December, 2 of 3, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Personal Newsclips January-December, 3 of 3, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Press Requests, 1 of 2, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Press Requests, 2 of 2, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Personal Newsclips January-June, 1 of 4, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Personal Newsclips January-June, 2 of 4, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Personal Newsclips January-June, 3 of 4, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Personal Newsclips January-June, 4 of 4, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Personal Newsclips June-December, 1 of 2, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Personal Newsclips June-December, 2 of 2, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Press Requests, 1 of 2, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Press Requests, 2 of 2, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Completed Interviews, 1 of 2, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Completed Interviews, 2 of 2, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Personal Newsclips January-March, 1 of 4, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Personal Newsclips January-March, 2 of 4, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Personal Newsclips January-March, 3 of 4, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Personal Newsclips January-March, 4 of 4, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Personal Newsclips April-November 12, 1 of 3, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Personal Newsclips April-November 12, 2 of 3, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Personal Newsclips April-November 12, 3 of 3, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Personal Newsclips November 13-21, 1 of 2, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Personal Newsclips November 13-21, 2 of 2, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Personal Newsclips November 22-December, 1 of 2, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Personal Newsclips November 22-December, 2 of 2, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Press Requests, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Press Requests, 1 of 2, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Press Requests, 2 of 2, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Personal Newsclips, 1 of 4, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Personal Newsclips, 2 of 4, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Personal Newsclips, 3 of 4, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Personal Newsclips, 4 of 4, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Personal Newsclips January-May, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Personal Newsclips June-December, 1 of 2, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Personal Newsclips June-December, 2 of 2, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Personal Newsclips September-December, 1 of 2, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Personal Newsclips September-December, 2 of 2, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Press Requests, 1 of 2, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Press Requests, 2 of 2, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Personal Newsclips January-May, 1 of 2, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Personal Newsclips January-May, 2 of 2, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Personal Newsclips June-December, 1 of 2, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Personal Newsclips June-December, 2 of 2, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, 2002-2005 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Press Requests, 1 of 3, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Press Requests, 2 of 3, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Press Requests,3 of 3, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Personal Newsclips January-May, 1 of 2, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Personal Newsclips January-May, 2 of 2, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Personal Newsclips June-December, 1 of 2, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Personal Newsclips June-December, 2 of 2, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Press Requests, 1 of 2, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Press Requests, 2 of 2, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Personal Newsclips, 1 of 3, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Personal Newsclips, 2 of 3, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Personal Newsclips, 3 of 3, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Press Requests, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Personal Newsclips, 1 of 4, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Personal Newsclips, 2 of 4, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Personal Newsclips, 3 of 4, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Personal Newsclips, 4 of 4, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Press Requests, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Personal Newsclips, 1 of 3, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Personal Newsclips, 2 of 3, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Personal Newsclips, 3 of 3, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Building Bridges Between the World of Ideas and the World of Action, 2006 (Box 43, Item 10)
    - Secretary Baker Book Tour October 12, 2006 (Box 43, Item 11)
    - Personal Newsclips, 1 of 4, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Personal Newsclips, 2 of 4, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Personal Newsclips, 3 of 4, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Personal Newsclips, 4 of 4, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - BP Press Conference January 16, 2007 (Box 43, Disc 16)
    - Sputnik, 2007 (Box 43, Item 17)
    - Personal Newsclips, 1 of 2, 2008 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Personal Newsclips, 2 of 2, 2008 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - CNN Presents The Next President: A World of Challenges September 20, 2008 (Box 43, Item 20)
    - ABC News Coverage of the Baker Institute October 31, 2008 (Box 43, Item 21)
    - CNN Interview with Campbell Brown June 3, 2009 (Box 43, Item 22)